{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5368","name":"Chubby Duck Detroit","address":"208 E Grand River","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Radial International LLC","licenseNumber":"217967","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Permanently Closed","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.00335,42.35021","geojson":{"id":"5368","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.00334968,42.350213007]},"properties":{"name":"Chubby Duck Detroit","owner":"Radial International LLC","address":"208 E Grand River","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"217967","establishmentid":"5368","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Permanently Closed","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/2/2017"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3171","name":"Delray Senior Pavillon","address":"275 Grand Blvd W","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"2593","name":"Moses Field School","address":"1100 Sheridan","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"2242","name":"Tim Hortons","address":"7201 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"5054","name":"Belle Isle Krispy Crunchy Chicken","address":"7255 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"777","name":"Curis Big Boy Restaurant","address":"7033 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1882","name":"City Pekin Chinese Food","address":"6905 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1188","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #345","address":"6931 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"4233","name":"St. Charles","address":"1491 Baldwin","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"1800","name":"Wendy's","address":"6601 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"5161","name":"Southern Fire Bistro & Lounge","address":"575 Bellevue St","zipcode":"48207"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"40882","inspectionDate":"2017-11-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-203.11","violationDescription":"(A)     FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES that are scaled only in Celsius or dually scaled in Celsius and Fahrenheit shall be accurate to ±1C in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n(B)     FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES that are scaled only in Fahrenheit shall be accurate to ±2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accurate","subProblem":"","location":"THERMOMETER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Calibrate to requirement above."}]},{"inspectionid":"38557","inspectionDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide labels that comply with law."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"At the Hot holding temperatures","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-04-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"At the Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"38066","inspectionDate":"2017-02-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"and the Prep sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"wall covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In prep area","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"Light bulb(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"juncture","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-04-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5368"}}